Guide to the Adrienne Keriotis Dickos Papers, 1986-1989 CTC.2003.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Adrienne Keriotis Dickos Papers
1986-1989
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Dickos, Adrienne
CTC.2003.02
6 Linear Feet (4 boxes)
This collection is comprised of the stage notebooks of Adrienne Keriotis Dickos, documenting plays she managed between 1986 and 1989 for several theater companies in the Pittsburgh area. The binders for each play contain materials such as annotated scripts, contact information for cast and crew members, promotional materials, stage and costume information, and stage diagrams.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Adrienne Keriotis Dickos in February 2003.
Biography
Adrienne Keriotis Dickos is an accomplished stage manager associated with a number of theatre tours and groups in the Pittsburgh area such as the Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival, the City Theatre Company, the American Ballet Theatre, the Pittsburgh Opera, and the Civic Light Opera, among others. Dickos is a native of Pittsburgh and received her M.A. from the University of Pittsburgh.
Previous Citation
Adrienne Keriotis Dickos Papers, 1986-1989, CTC.2003.02, Curtis Theatre Collection, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
The collection consists of eight stage manager's books with handwritten notations: three from the Three River's Shakespeare Festival (TRSF), two from the Pittsburgh Playhouse, two from the Studio Theatre, and one from the South Hills Theatre. The contents of each binder have been filed in their original order.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in the following series:
Series I. Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival, 1988-1989
Series II. Pittsburgh Playhouse, 1989
Series III. Studio Theatre at the University of Pittsburgh, 1986
Series IV. South Hills Theatre, 1987
Performing arts -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Stage management; College theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Theater; Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Dickos, Adrienne; University of Pittsburgh. Department of Theatre Arts; Point Park College; Pittsburgh Playhouse. School of the Theater; Shakespeare, William -- Stage history -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh
- Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival, 1988-1989; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  Three stage manager's books with handwritten notations from the 1989 tour of Hamlet, the July/August 1989 production of Antony and Cleopatra, and the June 1988 production of the Taming of the Shrew.
  - Hamlet, 1989; 1.
    - Binder Notes and Attachments, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Script - Act I, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Script - Act II, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Script - Act III, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Script - Act IV, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Script - Act V, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Notes / Memos / Meetings, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - PR, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Props, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Costumes, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Sets, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Sound, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Lights, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Rehearsal and Performance Reports, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Contact, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Company Manual, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Schedules, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Blank Forms and Letterhead, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Copy of Script for Sharon, Pennsylvania, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Stage Map, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Run Sheets, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Tax Exemption Letter, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Anthony and Cleopatra, July-August 1989; 2.
    - Binder Labels and Attachments, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Schedules, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Script - Act I, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Script - Act II, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Script - Act III, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Script - Act IV, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Script - Act V, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Notes, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Meetings and Memos, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - PR, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Props, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Costumes, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Sets, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Sound / Lights, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Rehearsal and Performance Reports, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Contact, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Tax Exemption Letter, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Blank Forms and Letterhead, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 10th Anniversary Program, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Taming of the Shrew, June 1988; 3.
    - Stage Diagrams, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Script - Act I, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Script - Act II, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Script - Act III, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Script - Act IV, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Script - Act V, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Contact, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Schedules, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Rehearsal and Performance Reports, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Memos and Meetings, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Cue Sheets, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - PR, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Tour, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Company Manual, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Blank Forms, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Equity, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Scene / Character Breakdown, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Program, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Stage Diagram, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Recipt for Borrowed Equipment, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Two Gentlemen of Verona Chart, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Pittsburgh Playhouse, 1989; II.
  Two stage manager's books with handwritten notations from the October/November 1989 production of the Mystery of Edwin Drood and the March 1989 production of Chicago.
  - Mystery of Edwin Drood, October-November 1989; 1.
    - Binder Notes and Attachments, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Schedules, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Script Notes, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Script - Prologue, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Script - Act I, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Script - Act II, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - APN, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Contact, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Rehearsal and Performance Reports, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Auditions, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Memos and Meetings, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Sets and Props, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Costumes, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Lights / Sound / Music, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Blank Forms and Letterhead, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Stage Map, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Equity, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Tax Exemption Certificate, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Script Excerpts, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Chicago, March 1989; 2.
    - Binder Photocopies and Attachments, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Script - Act I, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Script - Act II, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Contact, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Rehearsal and Performance Reviews, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Memos and Meetings, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Props, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Cue Sheets, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Ground Plans, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Schedules, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Equity, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Auditions, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Cast List, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Attendance Charts, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Tax Exemption Certificate, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Blank Forms and Letterhead, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Stage and Sound Diagrams, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Scene Breakdowns, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Rehearsal Signs, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Studio Theatre at the University of Pittsburgh, 1986; III.
  Two stage manager's books with handwritten notations from the March 1986 production of Betrayal and the November 1986 production of Grease.
  - Betrayal, March 1986; 1.
    - Annotated Script, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Prop List / Costume Plot / Stage Diagrams, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Program, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Grease, November 1986; 2.
    - Score with Choreography, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Contacts, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - PR, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Programs, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Rehearsal and Performance Reviews, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Schedules, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Lists, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Script, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Props, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Script with Sound Notations, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Set, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Tech, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- South Hills Theatre, 1987; IV.
  One stage manager's book with handwritten notations from the October 1987 production of Musical Feat.
  - Musical Feat - Binder Photocopies and Attachments, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Musical Feat - Annotated Script, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Musical Feat - Promotional Flyers, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Musical Feat - Contact, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Musical Feat - Program, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Musical Feat - Current Running Order, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Musical Feat - Notes, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 27)